<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Planning Poker</string>
    <string name="setting">setting</string>
    <string name="about">"?"</string>
    <string name="information">i</string>
    <string name="label_information">Information</string>
    <string name="label_about">About</string>
    <string name="label_privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="what_is_planning_poker">Planning Poker is an agile estimating and planning technique that is consensus
        based. To start a poker planning session, the product owner or customer reads an agile user story or describes a
        feature to the estimators.\n
        \n
        Each estimator is holding a deck of Planning Poker cards with values like 1/2, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 10, 15 and 20,
        which is the sequence we recommend. The values represent the number of story points, ideal days, or other units
        in which the team estimates.\n
        \n
        The estimators discuss the feature, asking questions of the product owner as needed. When the feature has been
        fully discussed, each estimator privately selects one card to represent his or her estimate. All cards are then
        revealed at the same time.
        \n
        \n
        If all estimators selected the same value, that becomes the estimate. If not, the estimators discuss their
        estimates. The high and low estimators should especially share their reasons. After further discussion, each
        estimator reselects an estimate card, and all cards are again revealed at the same time.
    </string>
    <string name="introduce_splash">Planning Poker is an agile estimating and planning technique that is consensus
        based. To start a poker planning session, the product owner or customer reads an agile user story or describes a
        feature to the estimators.</string>
    <string name="app_version">"@ 2019 H2 Co., Ltd."</string>
    <string name="app_show_info">Planning Poker %1$s</string>
    <string name="greetings_from_dev">Hi friends,\n
        \n
        Thank you for supporting me.\n
        \n
        If you have a question about Planning Poker or whatever you want an app looks like? I’m looking forward to hearing from you!\n
        Let me know what’s on your mind and I’ll get back to you soon.\n
        \n
        H2 Co., Ltd Developer
    </string>
    <string name="greetings">Greetings</string>
</resources>
